<resources>

    <string name="app_name">FPV-VR for wifibroadcast</string>

    <string name="SuperSyncDescription">Advanced VR rendering technique, modified for FPV-VR. Lowest input lag possible (8.3ms), without any visual imperfections
        like tearing. Has high performance and hardware requirements, that are only fulfilled on high-end phones. I recommend a Daydream-ready device.
        If you enable this technique on non-daydream ready phones, you might see stuttering and/or tearing.
    </string>
    <string name="DisableVSYNCDescription">
        Disables VSYNC (Vertical Sync). Reduces input lag to ~16.6ms@120fps or less, depending on your hardware (higher fps->less latency).
        WARNING: Has the negative side effect of Tearing (Visual imperfections) and wasted frames  It is up to you if you can live with tearing for a lower
        latency, but I definitely recommend enabling this option if available.
    </string>
    <string name="Disable60FPSLockDescription">
        VSYNC on (no tearing), but >60 OpenGL fps (lower latency). Input lag is at ~33.2ms@120fps.
        WARNING: when your phone has trouble rendering at >60fps, enabling this option can increase latency. Also, disabling VSYNC gives much lower latency.
    </string>
    <string name="MSAADescription">
        MSAA increases quality with very little performance loss.
        Which MSAA level to choose depends on your GPU power, screen resolution and magnification of your VR headset.
        Most modern tile-based GPUs can handle up to 4xMSAA with only 10-20perc. performance loss, while increasing quality significantly.
    </string>

    <string name="IPDDescription">Set to zero when you do not want to have an 3D Effect;for each Person different, but a default value of 0.2 seems to be optimal</string>

    <string name="EZWBDescription">Connect via UDP (Network Protocol) to your WB FPV receiver (rpi). When you connected successfully, you can see
        counter(s) indicating how much data has been received. </string>
    <string name="ManuallyDescription">Connect via UDP (Network Protocol) to any FPV receiver. Since UDP is unidirectional the app
    can only check if data arrives at the specified UDP ports. </string>
    <string name="AssetsFileDescription">Play a test video/telemetry file (included in the app) to test your decoder</string>
    <string name="StorageFileDescription1">Play video/telemetry from files in your internal storage (Ground Recording).</string>
    <string name="StorageFileDescription2">You can find your ground recording files in \"DCIM\\FPV_VR\".
        \nTo sync files with windows, connect your phone as "camera device".
        \nEnter your file names (e.g. 11-04-2019 16-33-42 are creation date and time)
        \nThey have to be in the right format and sit in your FPV_VR folder\n</string>

    <string name="RTSPDescription">In development. Enter valid RTSP string (or other string that can be played by ffmpeg), then start video playing activity.</string>

    <string name="DJIDescription">DJI In development.</string>

    <string name="Mode1_Description">Mode 1: Connect to EZ-WB/OpenHD RX Pi via Wifi</string>
    <string name="Mode2_Description">Mode 2: Connect to EZ-WB/OpenHD RX Pi via USB cable</string>

    <string name="EZWBMode1Info">Connect your mobile phone to EZ-WB/OpenHD RX Pi via Wifi
            \n1)On your RX PI (wifibroadcast-1 file): WIFI_HOTSPOT=Y; VIDEO_UDP_PORT=5600;
            \n  Start RX and TX PIs
            \n2)On your Phone: Activate Wifi and connect to \"EZ-WifiBroadcast\" using \"wifibroadcast\" as passphrase
            \n Or \"OpenHD\" using \"wifiopenhd\" as passphrase
            \n3)If your RX Pi also has a display connected: Wait for \"Secondary Display Connected\" message to appear on
            your RX Pi Monitor</string>
    <string name="EZWBMode2Info">Connect your Mobile Phone to EZ-WB/OpenHD RX Pi via USB cable
            \n1)On your RX PI (wifibroadcast-1 file): VIDEO_UDP_PORT=5600;
            \n  Start RX and TX PIs
            \n2)Connect your Phone to the RX Pi via USB Cable
            \n3)On your Phone: Enable \"USB tethering\" (now the Phone acts as Hotspot via USB and the RPI automatically connects)
            \n4)If your RX Pi also has a display connected: Wait for \"Secondary Display Connected\" Message to appear on
            your RX Pi Monitor</string>
    <string name="ManuallyInfo">Connect your Mobile Phone to any Digital FPV setup (ADVANCED)
            \n1)Create a Network connection between your digital receiver and your phone
            \n2)On your receiver, forward rtp h264 video stream via UDP to Port 5600 and Telemetry to the equivalent Ports (5001,5001 usw)
            \n or raw h264 video stream via UDP to Port 5600 when disabling parseRTP
    </string>
    <string name="Info_ConnectEZWBOPNEHD">
        Connect to EZ-WifiBroadcast with PW=wifibraodcast or OpenHD with PW=wifiopenhd
    </string>



    <string name="PerformanceHacksDescription">PLEASE READ CAREFULLY BEFORE CHANGING VALUES !
    </string>

    <string name="DisbaleLowPersistenceModeDescription">Low persistence mode slightly decreases your perceived display response time
        (and therefore latency) but makes your screen flickery. Disable it here if you dont like it. Only has an effect when SuperSync is enabled.
    </string>
    <string name="button_network_settings">NETWORK</string>
</resources>
